Delmar Progress Club; Records mss148
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Events, 1913-2021, Undated; 2; 1.45 cubic ft.
  - Delmar Progress Club, State Convention, The Sitting, 2012 (Dvd 7)
  - Photographs, New Member Orientation, 2015 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, Club Function, Unidentified, 2016 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Performing Arts Group, Salute to Broadway, 2016; Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - March Down Memory Lane, 2018; Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - New Member Orientation, 2019 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Club's 120th Anniversary, ca. 2021 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Notes on 85th Anniversary, 90th Anniversary Rehearsal, and 95th Anniversary DVDs, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Publications, 1904-2019, Undated; 1.0 cubic ft.
  This series only includes publications of the Delmar Progress Club and contains an incomplete run of the Delmar Progress Club's newsletter and a complete set of the Club yearbook from 1904 to 2019. Although the newsletter did not initially have a title, by August 1988, it was named Progress in Print. Starting in 2006, receipts for the printing of Progress in Print are included with the newsletters. An issue of the Club yearbook typically contains a message from the Club president, announcements, lists of Club and General Federation of Women's Clubs officers, lists of committees and committee members, a Club calendar, a general Club program, a list of past Club presidents, member phone directory, and standing rules of the Club. Copies of the yearbook may also contain loose documents, i.e. Club by-laws, by-laws revisions, correspondence to the members, dues statements, event invitations, and membership lists.
  - Club Yearbooks, 1904-1910 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Club Yearbooks, 1910-1919 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Club Yearbooks, 1920-1930; Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Club Yearbooks, 1930-1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Club Yearbooks, 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Club Yearbooks, 1950-1960; Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Club Yearbooks (Part 1 of 2), 1960-1970; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Club Yearbooks (Part 2 of 2), 1960-1970; Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Club Yearbooks, 1970-1980; Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Club Yearbooks, 1980-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Club Newsletter and Progress in Print, 1986-1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Club Yearbooks, 1990-2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Progress in Print, 1998-2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Club Yearbooks, 2000-2010 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Progress in Print, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Progress in Print, 2006-2010 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Club Yearbooks (Part 1 of 2), 2010-2019 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Club Yearbooks (Part 2 of 2), 2010-2019 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Progress in Print, 2011-2012 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Progress in Print, 2012-2013; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Progress in Print, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Progress in Print, Mailing Lists, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Progress in Print, 2016-2019; Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Subject Files, 1913-2021, Undated; 7.16 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Documents in subject files include materials relating to the General Federation of Women's Clubs (GFWC) and its New York subsidiary (those not used in the Club's regular administrative procedures); awards, certificates, and citations awarded to the Club by its two parent organizations and outside groups; materials such as biographical documents and newspaper clippings about prominent Club officers; newspaper materials about the election and installation of Club officers; materials relating to the Club's longstanding relationship with the Bethlehem Public Library; newspaper clippings about the Club's involvement in Bethlehem and Delmar, New York; Bethlehem Board of Education and town board meeting minutes and Club reports on those meetings; Club environmental initiatives and projects, notably the Home Energy Check Scrapbook and the Club's recycling project in Bethlehem; Club histories compiled and written by various Club members; the records of the Club Travel Group (such materials include thank you cards from Club members for trips, correspondence with hotels and travel companies, event tickets, reports on sites of interest, trip itineraries, lists of Club members going on trips and lists of roommates, photo albums, photographs, and financial information about trips); and records relating to the Club's charity work with local programs, including the Bethlehem school backpack program and Bethlehem Senior Projects, and outside charitable organizations, including Canine Companions, HOBY, and the March of Dimes. This series also includes various scrapbooks chronicling Club activities compiled by members from 1929 to 2016; these contain issues of the Club newsletter, copies of the Club yearbook, magazine and newspaper clippings, photographs, Club spring and fall banquet programs, invitations, programs, and registration forms for other events, intra-Club and extra-Club correspondence, certificates and citations from the Club's parent organizations and outside groups, contest prizes, proposed amendments to the Club's by-laws, Club reports, Club schedules, brochures from and maps of places the Travel Group visited, and additional materials from the Club's parent organizations. In addition, this series contains a family directory of Delmar, New York compiled by the Club in June 1913. Finally, the series contains an audio cassette tape, CDs, DVDs, and various artifacts used by the Club and its members. Please note that the New York division of the General Federation of Women's Clubs is known by a few names in the series, including General Federation of Women's Clubs - New York, General Federation of Women's Clubs - New York State Federation of Women's Clubs, and simply the New York State Federation of Women's Clubs.
  - Addition of Study Groups in 1969, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alice Porter's History and Memorabilia, 1949-2001; Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Red Cross' Good Neighbor Award, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bethlehem Bicentennial Celebrations, 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bethlehem Celebrates U.S. Bicentennial, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bethlehem Central School District Backpack Program, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bethlehem Central School Board, Meeting Minutes, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bethlehem Public Library, 1980-2013; Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bethlehem Public Library, Lobby Display, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bethlehem Senior Projects, 2012; Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bethlehem Senior Projects, Pin, Volunteer Star, ca. 2017 (Artifact-box 1)
  - Bethlehem Town Board, Meeting Minutes and Reports, 2001-2002; Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bethlehem Town Clerk's Reply To Delmar Progress Club's Letter and Petition, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Carine Companions, 2015-2016; Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Catherine Van Valkenburgh For Club Women of The Year, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Certificate to General Federation of Women's Clubs - New York from Heifer International, 2017 (Oversized 8, Folder 1)
  - Certificates and Letters of Congratulations for the Club's 100th Anniversary, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Club Embosser with Leather Pouch, Undated (Artifact-box 1)
  - Club History 1901-1937, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Club History 1970 to 1991 and 2000 to 2010, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Club Recycling Project and General Federation of Women's Clubs Award Entry, 1988-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Family Directory of Delmar, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Flea Market To Raise Seed Money for Scholarship and '79 State Convention, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, 60th Anniversary Pamphlet, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, 125th Anniversary, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, 2012 to 2014 Club Manual, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, Brochures, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, Centennial Celebration, 1987-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, Centennial Club, Gavel, ca. 1990 (Artifact-box 1)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, Certificates, Citations, and Scrolls, 2001-2002; Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, Clubwoman, 1984; 2001 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, Epsilon Sigma Omicron, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, Free Enterprise Program and Award, 1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, Jennie June Mother of Clubs, Script, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs - New York, 2016 to 2018 Directory, 2011-2016; Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs - New York, Annual Reports (Part 1 of 2), 2012-2013; 2015-2019 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs - New York, Annual Reports (Part 2 of 2), 2012-2013; 2015-2019 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs - New York, Awards and Certificates, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs - New York, Club Reporting Forms, 2004; 2006-2008; 2010-2018; Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs - New York, Empire Focus, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs - New York, Scroll, Club's 120th Anniversary, 2021 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs - New York State Federation of Women's Clubs, Citations and Scrolls, 1961; 1976; 1991; Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs - New York State Federation of Women's Clubs, Conference and Events, 2009; 2012-2019; Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs - New York State Federation of Women's Clubs, Contests and Awards, 2011-2018; Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs - New York State Federation of Women's Clubs, Dues Statements, 2012-2017; Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs - New York State Federation of Women's Clubs, Order of the Rose, 2017-2019; Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, Our Cultural Heritage in American Dress, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, Song Lyrics, Undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, Souvenir Program Book, 1916; Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, State Convention, 2001; Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Home Energy Check Summary Scrapbook, 1980; Undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Hugh O'Brian Youth Leadership, 2007-2009; 2011; 2013-2014; Undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - In Memory of Dorothy Margaret Hinsdale, Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Informal Review of 2 Books of Minutes from 1903 to 1910 and 1920 to 1923, 2021 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - March of Dimes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Mary Stewart's Collect for Club Women, 1981; Undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - "Memories of Delmar" Program, 1985 (Cassette 1)
  - Mrs. Boynton's History 1901 to 1936, Undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Mrs. Margaret Reynolds Hay, Undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Antique Study Group, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Bethlehem Central School District Budget, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Christmas Tree Controversy at Bethlehem Public Library, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Election and Installation of Club Officers, 1983-2014; Undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Newspapers Clippings, Exer-dance in Delmar, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Newspaper Clippings, General Federation of Women's Clubs, Diamond Jubilee, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Government Council, 1984; 1987 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Growth of Bethlehem, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Literature Group, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Lois Dillon, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Muriel Welch's Obituary, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Newspaper Clippings, New York State Legislative Forum, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Newspaper Clippings, New York State Federation of Women's Clubs, 1931-1932; 1984; 1986-1988; 1996 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Newspaper Clippings, "Progress Club Members Make Service a Priority", 1993 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Newspaper Clippings, "Progress Club Tackles Many Tasks", 2013 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Rosemary Brown, 2014; Undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Study Groups Meetings and Programs, 1939; 1986; 1988 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Vivian Bennett, 1987; Undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - New York State Federation of Women's Clubs, Awards and Citations, 1996-2000; Undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - New York Federation of Women's Club, Centennial, 1994; Undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - New York State Federation of Women's Club, District Map, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - New York State Federation of Women's Clubs, The Formers, 1989; 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - New York State Federation of Women's Clubs Materials, 1948-1964; Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - New York State Federation of Women's Clubs, New York State Clubwoman, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - New York State Federation of Women's Clubs, Roster of Clubs, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Photo Album #1 (Part 1 of 2), 1994-1996; Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Photo Album #1 (Part 2 of 2), 1994-1996; Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Photo Album #2 (Part 1 of 2), 1996-1998; Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Photo Album #2 (Part 2 of 2), 1996-1998; Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Photo Album #3 (Part 1 of 2), 1998-2002; Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Photo Album #3 (Part 2 of 2), 1998-2002; Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Photo Album #4 (Part 1 of 2), 2004-2008; Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Photo Album #4 (Part 2 of 2), 2004-2008; Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Photo Album #5 (Part 1 of 3), Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Photo Album #5 (Part 2 of 3), Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Photo Album #5 (Part 3 of 3), Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Photo Album #6, 2002; Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Photo Album, Travel Group, 1995; 1998-2001; 2005-2013; Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Photo Album, Travel Group, Cape Ann Trip, 2013 (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
  - Photo Album, Travel Group, Long Island Trip, 2014 (Oversized 1, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Amsterdam Tree Festival, 2016 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Photographs and Video Clips, Club Activities, 2018 (Dvd 9)
  - Photographs, Antique Study Group, Creamware, What Is It, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Antique Study Group, Mystery Trip, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, Antique Study Group, Trip to Adirondacks, 1989; Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Antique Study Group, Trip to Hartford, CT, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, Antique Study Group, Trip to Lindenwald, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Bethlehem Bicentennial Labor Day Parade and Antique Study Group, Trip on Hudson River, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, Bethlehem Historical Association, Sign and Costumes, 2010 (Cd 1)
  - Photographs, Board of Directors Meeting, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, Boston Flower Show, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, Boxwood Tree Project, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Photographs by Carol Smith, 2013; 2018 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Photographs by Carolyn Bennet, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, Canine Companions, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, Club Christmas Decorations at Ten Broeck Mansion, Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Photographs, Club Christmas Tree at Festival of Trees, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Photographs, Club Decorations for SR Luncheon, 2011; Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Photographs, Club Events and Scrapbooks, 2012-2013 (Cd 2)
  - Photographs, Club Garden at Bethlehem Public Library, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Photographs, Club Giving Tree, 2014; Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Photographs, Club Members Decorating Library for Christmas, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Photographs, Club Members in Costume, 2004; Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Photographs, Club Members Making Flowers, Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Photographs, Club Members Participating in Ms. Phonathon, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Photographs, Club Members Planting Daffodil Bulbs at Bethlehem Public Library, 1988; Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Photographs, Club Officers, Installation Ceremony, ca. 1992; ca.; Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Photographs, Creative Arts and Garden Group, Teddy Bear Project, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Photographs, Creative Arts Group, Artist Card Making, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Photographs, Creative Arts Group, Band Boxes, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Photographs, Creative Arts Group, Dreamscapes at Edna McCoy's and Festival Arts, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Photographs, Creative Arts Group, Have Hats Will Travel, Beginning Quilting, 3rd District Festival, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Photographs, Creative Arts Group, Let's Paint a Basket, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Photographs, Creative Arts Group, Painted Rug, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Photographs, Elizabeth White Receives New York State Federation of Women's Clubs Life Membership Certificate, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Photographs, Garden Club, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Photographs, General Federation of Women's Clubs, National and International Conferences, Undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Photographs, General Federation of Women's Clubs-New York, State Conventions, 1988-2006; Undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Photographs, Government Council Program, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Photographs, Identified Club Members, 1988-2017; Undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Photographs, Informal Club Dinners, 1990-2007; Undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Photographs, Music Study Group, All About the Harp, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Photographs, Music Study Group, The Organ at Round Lake, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Photographs, New Club Officers, 1977; 1982-1983; 1998 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Photographs, Resolutions Committee, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Photographs, Service Program, Glenmont Jobs Corps, ca. 1998 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Photographs, Tour of Five Rivers Environmental Center, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Photographs, Travel Group, 2005; 2010-2012 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Photographs, Travel Group, Jean Lyon and Shirley Dunqin in Indonesia and Bali, 1995; Undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Photographs, Trips and Activities, Unidentified, 1995; Undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Photographs, Trips, General, Unknown Photographer, 1995-1996; 1998-2002; 2005-2008; Undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Photographs, Trip to Annapolis and Baltimore, 2001; Undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Photographs, Trip to Bristol Harbor, 2016 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Photographs, Trip to Cape Ann, 2013; Undated (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Photographs, Trip to Cape May, 2009; Undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Photographs, Trip to Corning and Finger Lakes, 2006; Undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Photographs, Trip to Gettysburg, 1999; Undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Photographs, Trip to Granger Homestead and Carriage Museum, 2016 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Photographs, Trip to Hildene, Undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Photographs, Trip to Island, 1995; Undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Photographs, Trip to Mansions and Luncheon, 2012; Undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Photographs, Trip to Mystic, CT, 2003; Undated (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Photographs, Trip to New Mexico, 2014 (Dvd 8)
  - Photographs, Trip to Niagara-on-the-Lake, 2008; Undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Photographs, Trip to Old Deerfield, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Photographs, Trip to Ogunquit, ME, 2011; Undated (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Photographs, Trip to Ottawa, 2010; Undated (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Photographs, Trip to Ottawa, 2010 (Cd 3)
  - Photographs, Trip To Oyster Bay, 2014; Undated (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Photographs, Trip to Philadelphia, 2007; Undated (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Photographs, Trip to Pine Hollow Arboretum, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Photographs, Trip to Providence, RI, 2003; Undated (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Photographs, Trip to Toronto, 1999; Undated (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Photographs, Trip to Vermont, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Photographs, Trip to Vermont, 2012; Undated (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Photographs, Trip to Washington, D.C., 2005; Undated (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Photographs, Trip To Washington D.C., 2011 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Trip to Westbury Gardens, ca. 1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Trips, Unidentified, 2011; Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Unidentified Club Functions, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, Unidentified Club Members, 1988-2016; Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Unidentified Presenter, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Plaque Commemorating Bethlehem Library, 1997; Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook #1, 1925; 1929-1931; 1933-1939; 1942-1943; Undated (Oversized 2, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook #, 1 Loose Materials, 1934; 1936-1937; 1939; 1942; Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook #2, 1932-1933; Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook #3, 1906; 1944-1951; 1965; Undated (Oversized 2, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook # 3, Loose Materials, 1906; 1947-1950; 1965; Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Scrabook #4, 1951-1959; 1975; 1984; 2003; Undated (Oversized 3, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook #4, Loose Materials, 1952-2003; Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook #5, 1935; 1949-1963; Undated (Oversized 3, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook #5, Loose Materials, 1935; 1949; 1953-1957; 1960-1963; Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook #6, 1915; 1954; 1960-1962; Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook #6, Loose Materials, 1915; 1954; 1961; Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook #7 (1 of 8), 1962-1970; Undated (Oversized 8, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook #7 (2 of 8), 1962-1970; Undated (Oversized 8, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook #7 (3 of 8), 1962-1970; Undated (Oversized 8, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook #7 (4 of 8), 1962-1970; Undated (Oversized 8, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook #7 (5 of 8), 1962-1970; Undated (Oversized 8, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook #7 (6 of 8), 1962-1970; Undated (Oversized 8, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook #7 (7 of 8), 1962-1970; Undated (Oversized 8, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook #7 (8 of 8), 1962-1970; Undated (Oversized 8, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook #7, Loose Materials, 1962-1966; Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook #8, 1970-1981; Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook #8, Loose Materials, 1972; 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook #9, 1954; 1982-1988; Undated (Oversized 5, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook #9, Loose Materials, 1986-1987; Undated (Oversized 8, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook #10, 1988-1993; 2010; Undated (Oversized 5, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook #10, Loose Materials, 1989-1993; 2010; Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook #11, 1989; 1993-1994; Undated (Oversized 6, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook #11, Loose Materials, 1989; 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook #12, 2009-2013; Undated (Oversized 6, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook #12, Loose Materials, 2009-2010; 2012-2013 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Scrapbook #13, 2013-2016; Undated (Oversized 7, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook #14, 2016-2017; Undated (Oversized 7, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, General Federation of Women's Clubs, FREE Club Scrapbook Contest Entry, 1985; 1988-1990; Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Slides, Old Dresses at Bethlehem Historic Association, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Slides, Old Dresses at Bethlehem Historic Association, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Slides, Vintage Costumes, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Travel Group, Rough Drafts of Submissions to Club Yearbook, Report, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Travel Group, Trips, 1995-2002; Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Travel Group, Trips, 2002-2014; 2016; Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)